<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Namma Bengaluru Pulse</string>

    <!-- City Introduction -->
    <string name="city_name">Bengaluru</string>
    <string name="city_intro">
        Bengaluru, known as the Silicon Valley of India, is a vibrant metropolis that effortlessly blends rich cultural heritage with modern innovation. Whether you\'re a food lover, nature enthusiast, techie, or explorer, the city offers a colorful palette of experiences to suit every traveler’s pulse.
    </string>
    <string name="City_image_intro">Silicon Valley of India</string>

    <!-- Coffee Shops -->
    <string name="coffee_shop_category">Coffee Shops</string>
    <string name="third_wave">Third Wave Coffee Roasters</string>
    <string name="third_wave_desc">A modern, indie-style café popular among remote workers and students. Known for its specialty brews, cozy interiors, and calm ambiance — perfect for both focused work and casual chats.</string>

    <string name="matteo">Matteo Coffea</string>
    <string name="matteo_desc">Located near Church Street, this café boasts stylish interiors and a strong European vibe. Ideal for coffee connoisseurs and people-watching alike, with great blends and bakery options.</string>

    <string name="hatti_kaapi">Hatti Kaapi</string>
    <string name="hatti_kaapi_desc">A go-to for South Indian filter coffee served in traditional steel tumblers. A fast, no-frills place that delivers bold flavors with authentic local charm.</string>

    <string name="dyu">DYU Art Café</string>
    <string name="dyu_desc">A serene courtyard café infused with art and culture. Set in a traditional South Indian home, it\'s perfect for those who seek a quiet, creative space to unwind with books and coffee.</string>

    <string name="blue_tokai">Blue Tokai Coffee Roasters</string>
    <string name="blue_tokai_desc">A favorite among the hip crowd, this place roasts its own beans on-site and serves them in a minimalist, modern space. Try their cold brews or pourovers with a fresh bakery treat.</string>

    <!-- Restaurants -->
    <string name="restaurant_category">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="toit">Toit</string>
    <string name="toit_desc">One of Bengaluru’s most iconic brewpubs. A vibrant mix of craft beer, fusion food, and energetic ambiance. Great for weekend evenings and casual celebrations with friends.</string>

    <string name="mtr">MTR (Mavalli Tiffin Room)</string>
    <string name="mtr_desc">A legendary vegetarian restaurant offering classic South Indian meals since 1924. Try their Rava Idli, masala dosa, and filter coffee — steeped in culinary tradition.</string>

    <string name="truffles">Truffles</string>
    <string name="truffles_desc">Casual dining hotspot with crowd-favorite burgers, steaks, and pastas. A hit among students and young professionals for its taste, value, and lively atmosphere.</string>

    <string name="koshys">Koshy’s</string>
    <string name="koshys_desc">A timeless eatery that has hosted generations of writers, artists, and thinkers. The vintage colonial vibe pairs beautifully with comfort food and rich conversations.</string>

    <string name="black_rabbit">The Black Rabbit</string>
    <string name="black_rabbit_desc">Trendy and upbeat, this modern bar serves fusion dishes, craft cocktails, and features live music nights. Perfect for date nights or evening hangouts.</string>

    <!-- Parks -->
    <string name="parks_category">Parks</string>
    <string name="cubbon_park">Cubbon Park</string>
    <string name="cubbon_park_desc">A sprawling green lung in the city’s center. Popular for morning jogs, weekend picnics, and quiet escapes amidst colonial-era architecture and old trees.</string>

    <string name="lalbagh">Lalbagh Botanical Garden</string>
    <string name="lalbagh_desc">A 200+ year-old botanical garden featuring exotic plants, a serene lake, and the iconic glasshouse modeled after London’s Crystal Palace. A must-visit for nature lovers and photographers.</string>

    <string name="jp_park">JP Park</string>
    <string name="jp_park_desc">A community park in North Bengaluru with walking trails, a musical fountain, and an open-air gym. A peaceful family-friendly hangout spot away from the chaos.</string>

    <string name="bugle_rock">Bugle Rock Park</string>
    <string name="bugle_rock_desc">Famous for its natural rock formations said to be millions of years old. A calm park surrounding a historic watchtower, favored by locals for evening strolls.</string>

    <string name="bannerghatta">Bannerghatta Biological Park</string>
    <string name="bannerghatta_desc">A vast park home to a zoo, butterfly enclosure, and thrilling safari rides. Located on the citys outskirts, its ideal for a day trip with family or wildlife enthusiasts.</string>

    <!-- Kid-Friendly -->
    <string name="kid_friendly_category">Kid Friendly</string>
    <string name="bal_bhavan">Jawahar Bal Bhavan</string>
    <string name="bal_bhavan_desc">A dedicated children’s play area inside Cubbon Park with swings, rides, and a miniature toy train. Offers hours of joyful exploration for younger kids.</string>

    <string name="snow_city">Snow City</string>
    <string name="snow_city_desc">Beat the Bengaluru heat in this indoor snow park! Play with snow, slide down icy slopes, and enjoy an arctic experience in the heart of the city.</string>

    <string name="film_city">Innovative Film City</string>
    <string name="film_city_desc">A large amusement and film-themed park with attractions like a wax museum, cartoon city, haunted mansion, and mirror maze — perfect for a full day of family fun.</string>

    <string name="fun_world">Fun World</string>
    <string name="fun_world_desc">A classic amusement park that combines thrilling rides with a water park. Great for birthdays, school holidays, and all things splashy and exciting.</string>

    <string name="science_museum">Science Museum (Visvesvaraya)</string>
    <string name="science_museum_desc">Named after Sir M. Visvesvaraya, this interactive museum makes science fun through hands-on exhibits, physics demos, and immersive 3D shows for all ages.</string>

    <!-- Shopping -->
    <string name="shopping_category">Shopping</string>
    <string name="phoenix">Phoenix MarketCity</string>
    <string name="phoenix_desc">An expansive shopping mall in Whitefield with national and international brands, multiplex, food court, and live entertainment events. A complete leisure destination.</string>

    <string name="ub_city">UB City Mall</string>
    <string name="ub_city_desc">Bengaluru’s luxury shopping hub with high-end designer labels, gourmet restaurants, and a posh rooftop vibe. The city’s go-to for upscale retail therapy.</string>

    <string name="orion">Orion Mall</string>
    <string name="orion_desc">A modern mall located near Rajajinagar, featuring lakeside views, a vibrant food court, and popular fashion and electronics outlets. Great for weekend hangouts.</string>

    <string name="mantri">Mantri Square</string>
    <string name="mantri_desc">One of the largest malls in South India, connected to a metro station. Offers everything from budget shopping to big-brand showrooms, food courts, and multiplexes.</string>

    <string name="commercial_street">Commercial Street</string>
    <string name="commercial_street_desc">A lively street market for budget-friendly fashion, jewelry, and accessories. Crowded but exciting — perfect for bargain hunting and festive shopping.</string>
    <string name="City_image_desc">Silicon valley of India</string>
</resources>
